

#### PERSONAL INFORMATION

## Jefferson Salvador Costa

- Lisbon (Portugal)
- (+351) 939 081 877
- Skype jeffersonsalvador

### PERSONAL STATEMENT

Passionate about web development, I have over 10 years of experience using PHP / MySQL. I currently use resources relevant to code quality and performance.

- Proficient experience using PHP, MySQL;
- Good experience using Laravel and Vuejs;
- Knowledge of code versioning tools such as Git;

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

#### Dec 2017-Present

# Full Stack PHP Developer

PDMFC, Lisbon (Portugal)

- Working with graphic designers and converting designs to visual elements;
- Frontend with Vue.js, Quasar framework, Javascript;
- Backend with Laravel and MariaDB;

## Aug 2009-Dec 2017

## Full Stack Developer

Ineo Soluções Inteligentes (Brazil)

The Ineo Sistemas is a company especialized in web softwares and websites.

- Full stack development of applications with PHP/MySQL
- Development of responsive websites using Wordpress
- Starting the development of mobile applications

skills: PHP, Mysql, Bootstrap, Css3, Javascript, HTML5

### Jan 2008-Aug 2009

## Computer systems analyst

WCOM Consulting and Information Technology (Brazil)

Web developer at a company specialized in developing computerized information systems. Broad portfolio of projects in the United States and Hungary due to the high quality and good cost ratio offered to customers.

- PHP/MySQL;
- PSD to HTML/CSS;

#### **EDUCATION AND TRAINING**

### 2005-2008

# Bachelor's degree, Computer Systems Analysis

Faculdade Pitagoras, Divinopolis (Brazil)

#### PERSONAL SKILLS

#### Mother tongue(s)

Portuguese



### Curriculum vitae

### Jefferson Salvador Costa

### Foreign language(s)

Spanish English

UNDERSTANDING		SPEAKING		WRITING			
Listening	Reading	Spoken interaction	Spoken production				
B1	B1	A2	A2	A2			
B2	B2	B1	B1	B1			
EC TORONTO							

Levels: A1 and A2: Basic user - B1 and B2: Independent user - C1 and C2: Proficient user

Common European Framework of Reference for Languages

## Digital skills

SELF-ASSESSMENT						
Information processing	Communication	Content creation	Safety	Problem- solving		
Proficient user	Proficient user	Proficient user	Proficient user	Proficient user		

Digital skills - Self-assessment grid

### ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

Hard skills

- PHP7, Mysql, MariaDB, Laravel 5.5
- HTML5, CSS3, Less, Sass, Stylus, Gulp, Grunt, Webpack
- jQuery, Vue.js, Quasar framework
- RestAPI, Laradock, Docker, Git
- UX and UI

Soft skills

Proactive, creative, responsible, flexible and good relationship skills.

### Courses Alura Cursos Online

■ 876 h between 01/05/2016 and 29/11/2018: HTML5, CSS3, Javascript ES6, GIT, MySQL, PDO, Sass, Gulp, Vagrant, SEO, Laravel, Vue, Bootstrap, Gulp, Grunt, Docker, Vue.js, React.